nofraud.com 2019-02-22

# Privacy Policy

By using NoFraud LLC’s website (the “Website”), or any of the services offered thereby (the “Services”), you accept and agree the following privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”), and you are consenting to our collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of personal information as described in this Privacy Notice. If you do not provide the information we require, we may not be able to provide all of our Services to you. 

NoFraud LLC, (referred to herein as “NoFraud”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) values and respects your privacy rights and recognizes the importance of protecting your information. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains what personal data we collect from you and how we use it. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the NoFraud Terms of Use (<https://portal.nofraud.com/pages/terms-of-use>) and is subject to the terms therein, including but not limited to GDPR compliance requirements that may apply to you to the extent that you have customers that reside in the EU, or otherwise handle or otherwise have access to Personal Data (as that term is defined in Regulation (EU) 2016/679, generally known as the General Data Protection Regulation or GDPR). 

**1\. SCOPE.**

1.1 This Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information by us through the Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information not collected through the Services. 

1.2 "Personal information" is information that can be associated with a specific person and could be used to identify that specific person whether from that data or from that data and other information that NoFraud has or is likely to have access to. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been made anonymous or aggregated so that it can no longer be used to identify a specific person, whether in combination with other information or otherwise. 

**2\. COLLECTION.**

2.1 _How We Collect_. We may collect personal information from you when you use or access our Services, including but not limited to, when you sign up for the Services, when you send us credit card and personal information of your customers, or when you otherwise correspond with us or other users in connection with your use of the Services. 

2.2 _What We Collect_. The personal information we collect includes, but is not limited to, the following: 

•  Identifying information such as your name, address, phone numbers, and e-mail address; 

•  Financial information such as your bank account and credit card information; 

•  Information used to fulfill your transactions, such as the personal information of your customers; 

•  Device IDs or other unique identifiers; 

•  Usage statistics, page views, referral URLs, your IP address, and web log information; and 

•  Information collected via cookies and similar technologies. 

**3\. USE, RETENTION, AND CORRECTIONS.**

3.1 _How We Use Personal Information_. **We will never sell personal information to third-parties for advertising or marketing purposes.** Personal information you provide will be used to provide and improve the Services and to personalize the Services for you. This includes, but is not limited to, providing customer service, corresponding with you, and to protect the integrity and operation of the Services. 

3.2 _Duration of Retention_. We will keep personal information you provide as long as there is a reasonable basis to do so, whether to enforce any relevant law, the provisions of any agreement, to resolve any past, current, or future dispute, or any other business, tax, or legal purpose. When we dispose of personal information, we will do so in a secure manner. 

3.3 _Corrections_. You may request correction of any personal information that is incorrect by contacting us at [info@nofraud.com](mailto:info@nofraud.com). 

**4\. YOUR CHOICES.**

4.1 _You May Decline to Provide Information_. You may decline to submit personal information and/or disable webpage cookies. 

4.2 _Effect of Declining to Provide Information_. If you decline to submit personal information or any portion thereof, you may experience materially reduced Services quality, including but not limited to, the inability of NoFraud to validate Services transactions (which may result in your inability to make purchases) or provide chargeback protection. However, you acknowledge and agree that any resulting inability to provide the Services, or any resulting degradation thereof, shall not be grounds for any claim of breach, damages, or other liability; nor shall it in any way relieve you of your obligations to NoFraud. 

4.3 _You May Request Deletion of Personal Information_. You may request that NoFraud delete personal information (either your own, or a third-party’s at said third-party’s request). However, you acknowledge and agree that doing so shall relieve and release NoFraud from any liability, obligation, claim, or other damages related to or arising from said personal information, including but not limited to any obligation with respect to any disputed transactions. 

4.4 _No Sensitive Information._ You acknowledge and agree that the information you are providing to NoFraud for the purposes of performing the Services is not sensitive in nature (i.e., is not personal information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, etc.). 

**5\. LEVEL OF SECURITY.**

5.1 _How Secure It Is_. NoFraud shall use commercially reasonable measures inline with industry standards to protect your information, including but not limited to electronic and administrative safeguards designed to help make personal information secure. We will make reasonable attempts to provide you with notice in the event of a security breach. 

**6\. DISCLOSURE.**

6.1 _When Will We Disclose Personal Information_. We may share personal information with third-parties when necessary to provide the Services (such as to our vendors or to other users to enable transactions between users), when we have a good faith belief it is necessary by law or to respond to legal process, to protect the safety and lives of people, to protect the rights or property of NoFraud, in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, and with your consent. We shall not disclose personal information to third-parties for their advertising and marketing purposes absent your express consent. 

6.2 _Disclosure to Sub-Contractors and Agents._ NoFraud may use the services of other companies in order to provide the Services. Such companies shall be given only the personal information needed to perform those services, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes. We have contracts in place holding such companies to the same standards of confidentiality by which NoFraud is governed. NoFraud shall make commercially reasonable efforts to enforce such terms on such companies. However, NoFraud shall not be liable to you for such companies failure to adhere to such confidentiality terms. 

**7\. PRIVACY SHIELD FRAMEWORK.**   The following terms apply solely to transfers of personal data from the EU or Switzerland to the U.S. in connection with NoFraud’s provision of the Services.

7.1 _Participation._ NoFraud participates in the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks (the “Frameworks”). NoFraud is subject to said Frameworks with respect to personal information transferred from the EU and/or Switzerland to the U.S. See the list of participating entities (including NoFraud) at the following URL: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>. 

7.2. _Commitment to the Framework._ NoFraud is committed to subject to the Framework’ principles all personal data received from the EU in reliance on the Privacy Shield. 

7.3 _Your Right to Access Your Personal Data._ NoFraud shall honor bona fide, reasonable requests of persons in the EU or Switzerland to obtain a copy of the personal data that NoFraud has on record for him/her. 

7.4 _Independent Dispute Resolution Body._ Any disputes related to or arising from NoFraud’s participation in the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Frameworks shall be heard by the EU Data Protection Authorities or the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner, respectively. You my address complaints to such bodies and they will provide appropriate recourse free of charge to you. 

7.5 _Investigatory and Enforcement Powers._ This Agreement and the Services are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the FTC. 

7.6 _Binding Arbitration._ Per the terms of the Frameworks, under certain circumstances you may invoke binding arbitration. 

7.7 _Onward Transfers._ In cases of onward transfers of data, received pursuant to the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield, NoFraud is potentially liable. 

**8\. OTHER.**

8.1 _Your Customers._ To the extent that you are using the Services to verify transactions of your customers (“End Users”), without in any way limiting the warranties and license grants contained in the NoFraud Terms of Use, you agree to cause such End Users to agree to terms of service and a privacy policy that: a.) allow NoFraud to process End Users’ personal information on your behalf for the purpose of providing the Services; b.) are no less restrictive, and no less protective of NoFraud and NoFraud’s rights, as the terms of the NoFraud Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy; c.) adheres to the GDPR and any other applicable laws or regulations; and d.) is no less protective of the End Users’ personal information than the NoFraud Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. 

8.2 _Correcting Personal Information._ You agree to notify NoFraud of personal information that you are aware has errors. 

8.3 _Changes._ We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of our Services will signify your acceptance of any changes to our Privacy Policy. 

If there is a substantive or material change in the way that we use personal information, we will notify you via email of the relevant changes or provide other prominent notice. 

8.4 _Third-Parties._ This Privacy Policy applies to NoFraud’s use of personal information, but does not apply to the activities of any third-party. If you disclose personal information to others, whether as a result of any transaction on the Website (including with bidders, buyers, and sellers), or ad-click, or otherwise, their privacy policies and practices will apply. NoFraud shall not be liable or in any way otherwise responsible for any use of personal information by such third-parties. 

8.5 _Contact Us._ If you have any questions, concerns, or complaints related to or regarding the above please contact us at [info@nofraud.com](mailto:info@nofraud.com).
